const e={sections:[{header:{text:"Choose the right verb form in the past simple tense"},exercises:[{type:"test",question:"It ____ (to be) a very difficult job.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"was",2:"is",3:"were",4:"to be"}},{type:"test",question:"I ____ (to see) a girl yesterday. I think I know her.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"saw",2:"see",3:"seed",4:"has seen"}},{type:"test",question:"A lot of reporters ____ (to be) at the meeting last week.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"were",2:"was",3:"be",4:"are"}},{type:"test",question:"____ you buy his splendid house in 2015?",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"did",2:"do",3:"were",4:"have"}},{type:"test",question:"Last spring we ____ (to move) to Astana.",rightAnswerIds:["2"],answers:{1:"move",2:"moved",3:"did move",4:"was moved"}},{type:"test",question:"He ____ (not live) in Boston in 2011.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"didn't live",2:"didn't lived",3:"doesn't live",4:"not live"}},{type:"test",question:"When ____Ann finish school?",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"Did",2:"Was",3:"Is",4:"Has"}},{type:"test",question:"That house ____ (to lose) its roof in the storm five years ago.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"lost",2:"lose",3:"losed",4:"was losing"}},{type:"test",question:"Jenny ____ (to work) at a circus last autumn.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"worked",2:"works",3:"did work",4:"doesn't work"}},{type:"test",question:"We ____ (to find) a nice place on that island. It was great holidays.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"Found",2:"Finded",3:"Find",4:"finds"}},{type:"test",question:"When ____ Lucy decide to look for a new job?",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"did",2:"was",3:"-",4:"were"}},{type:"test",question:"My sister ____ (not help) me with the washing-up yesterday.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"didn't help",2:"don't help",3:"not help",4:"hadn't helped"}},{type:"test",question:"Lucy ____ (to study) at English school a month ago.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"studied",2:"studies",3:"did study",4:"studyies"}},{type:"test",question:"It ____ (to be) very difficult test. I ____ (to look up) many words in dictionary.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"was, looked up",2:"were, looked up",3:"was, was looking up",4:"was being"}},{type:"test",question:"George's father____ (to come) to us the day before yesterday.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"came",2:"come",3:"comed",4:"would come"}}]}]};export{e as default};
